Guide to the Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, DC records, 1980-2013 MS2230
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, DC records
1980-2013
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, DC
Federal City Performing Arts Association
MS2230
61 Linear Feet
This collection contains financial records, marketing material, recordings, photographs, meeting minutes, fundraising records, and production records that document the work of the Gay Men's Chorus of Washington DC. These records date from 1980-2013.
Restrictions on Access
Documents containing personally identifying information about members not already identified in publicly available documents are restricted for a period of 75 years form date of creation. Documents with such restricted information have been placed into boxes with an "R" designation and sequestered from the public for the period specified above.
In the case of officers and other members who are publicly identified in tax fillings, press releases, incorporation documents, and other documents generated by the GMCW which have been released to or are available to the general public shall not be subject to this restriction.
Acquisition Information
Donated by the Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, DC in 2008. A second donation arrived June 29, 2015 (Accession 2015.037).
Historical Note
The Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, DC (GMCW) is one of the area's most highly respected arts and community service organizations. It is also known as the Federal City Performing Arts Association (FCPAA). Its mission is to "entertain through excellent musical performance, to affirm the place of Gay people in society, and to educate about the Gay experience." It has more than 225 singing members, nearly 100 support volunteers, more than 400 subscribers, nearly 500 donors, and an annual audience of nearly 10,000. The Washington Post has called GMCW "one of the world's best male choruses." (March 2001)
GMCW was established in 1981 after the San Francisco Gay Men's Chorus' historic national tour and performance at the Kennedy Center Concert Hall. Following that concert, a handful of committed citizens decided it was important that Washington also have a chorus that would use music and entertainment to create a positive and affirming experience for members and audiences, while educating the community about the Gay experience and advocating for equal rights for all people, regardless of sexual orientation.
GMCW is at the forefront of the gay and lesbian choral movement. It sets a standard of excellence in the arts and community service as it achieves artistic excellence while simultaneously touching lives and changing hearts – both on stage and in the community. The Chorus has performed at a variety of venues throughout the Washington area including the Kennedy Center, the National Theatre, the Warner Theatre, Constitution Hall, the Lincoln Theatre, and Lisner Auditorium at the George Washington University. The Chorus also performed at President Clinton's second inaugural in 1996, and in 1998, toured three Scandinavian capitals. While in Scandinavia, GMCW was received by Sweden's Princess Christina to thank chorus members for singing in support of Noah's Ark, a Swedish AIDS services organization.
During its 20th anniversary season, GMCW performed at Carnegie Hall and Boston Symphony Hall in joint concerts with the New York City Gay Men's Chorus and the Boston Gay Men's Chorus. In December 2002, GMCW was honored to perform as part of the 25th annual Kennedy Center Honors in tribute to Elizabeth Taylor. This performance was televised nationwide, bringing the Chorus into millions of homes across the nation.
GMCW also has a commitment to commissioning new works for men's chorus. Recent examples include Changing Hearts by Alan Shorter for men's chorus and chamber orchestra, and Oseh Shalom by Paul Leavitt for men's chorus and brass quintet – both of which can be heard on our CD, Changing Hearts. GMCW has won a number of awards, including the prestigious Mayor's Arts Award for artistic excellence in 1989, a Distinguished Service Award from the Gay and Lesbian Activists Alliance in 2003, and a Capital Pride Directors Award for Arts in 2005.
The Chorus can be heard on a variety of recordings, including: Singing Free, Pride and Joy (nominated for both a WAMMIE and a GLAMMA award – given by the national Gay and Lesbian Music Association), Let It Shine!, And in That Moment, I Dream of a Time (winner of a 2002 WAMMIE Award), You've Got to be Carefully Taught: The Songs of Sondheim and Hammerstein, with two-time Tony-Award nominee Laura Benanti, and Changing Hearts, our Silver Anniversary Album.
Source: Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, DC website (http://www.gmcw.org/) retrieved 2006.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains financial records, marketing material, recordings, photographs, meeting minutes, fundraising records, and production records that document the origination and on-going work of the Gay Men's Chorus of Washington DC. These records date from 1980-2013.
Collection Organization
Organized in 7 series: Governance, Financial records, Marketing and development records, Productions, Audiovisual materials, Photographs, and 2015 donation [preliminary inventory].
Music -- Washington (D.C.); Gay men -- Washington (D.C.); Washington (D.C.); Choruses, Secular (Men's voices) -- Washington (D.C.); Photographs; Kubiak, Greg D. (Greg Dale); Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, DC; Federal City Performing Arts Association; American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers; Buhrman, Jeff
- Governance, 1981-2003; Series 1
  Arrangement
  Organized into two subseries: Meeting minutes and Administrative records
  Conditions Governing Access
  The folders found in a box with an "R" designation (R1-R5) are closed for 75 years from date of creation.
  Related Materials
  For additional Governance-related materials, please see Series 7, Subseries 1.
  - Meeting minutes, 1981-2009; Series 1 Subseries 1
    Arranged chronologically.
    General
    FCPAA are the initials for the Federal City Performing Arts Association. The FCPAA is another name underwhich the Gay Men's Chorus of Washington does business.
    - FCPAA minutes [1 of 2], 1981-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - FCPAA minutes [2 of 2], 1981-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - FCPAA minutes, 1985-1986; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - FCPAA minutes, 1986-1987; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - FCPAA minutes, 1987-1989; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - FCPAA official minutes, 1991-1992; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - FCPAA official minutes, 1992-1993; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - FCPAA minutes [1 of 2], 1993-1994; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - FCPAA minutes [2 of 2], 1993-1994; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - FCPAA minutes [1 of 2], 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Includes 5 inch floppy disk
    - FCPAA minutes [2 of 2], 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - FCPAA minutes [1 of 3], 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Includes 3 1/4 inch floppy disk
    - FCPAA minutes [2 of 3], 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - FCPAA minutes [3 of 3], 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - FCPAA minutes [1 of 2], 1996-1997; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - FCPAA minutes [2 of 2], 1996-1997; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - FCPAA minutes [1 of 2], 1997-1998; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - FCPAA minutes [2 of 2], 1997-1998; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - FCPAA minutes [1 of 2], 1998-1999; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - FCPAA minutes [2 of 2], 1998-1999; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - FCPAA minutes [1 of 3], 1998-2000; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - FCPAA minutes [2 of 3], 1998-2000; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - FCPAA minutes [3 of 3], 1998-2000; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - FCPAA minutes, 1999-2000; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - List of dues paying members, 1999-2000; Series 1 Suberies 1 (Box R5, Folder 9)
    - FCPAA Board of Directors, 2000-2001; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - FCPAA Board of Directors [1of 2], 2001-2002; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - FCPAA Board of Directors [2 of 2], 2001-2002; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - FCPAA Board of Directors meeting minutes [1 of 3], July 2001-June 2003; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - FCPAA Board of Directors meeting minutes [2 of 3], July 2001-June 2003; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - FCPAA Board of Directors meeting minutes [3 of 3], July 2001-June 2003; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - meeting minutes, 2004 February - 2009 May; Series 1 Subseries 1
      Scope and Contents
      These records are digital.
  - Administrative records, 1980-2005; Series 1 Subseries 2
    Arrranged alphabetically.
    - Annual reports, 1996-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Audience research, 2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Audience research, 2000-2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors and membership directories, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box R1, Folder 1)
    - Board of Trustees handbook, 2002-2004; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - By laws (permanent), 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Capital Club executive committee, 1988-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Capital Club statement of purpose, 1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Chorus survey and expenses research, 1999-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - DC corporate reports, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - DC Lottery, 1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - DC unemployment compensation, 1998-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Directory passwords correspondence, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Dun & Bradstreet, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Employment policies and benefits, 1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Equipment purchases, 1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - European tour proposal and responses, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - European tour survey #1, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Gay Men's Chorus Day proclamations, 1983-2004; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Insurance - workers' compensation/auto, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Insurance - workers' compensation and employers liability, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Music Director search, 1996-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Newsletter, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Official Policy Manual FCPAA, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Retreat, 1996-1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Rosters, 1982-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box R1, Folder 2)
    - Strategic planning, 1998-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - US Postal Service, 1998-2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Financial records, 1980-2003; Series 2
  For other Financial records, see Series 7, Subseries 2.
  - Bank statements and reports FY 1982, 1986-1991 [1/3], 1981-1991; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Bank statements and reports FY 1982, 1986-1991 [2/3], 1981-1991; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Bank statements and reports FY 1982, 1986-1991 [3/3], 1981-1991; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - General ledger FY 1981, 1980-1981; Series 2 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - General ledger FY 1982, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Financial records, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Deposit records and check registers [1/3], 1981-October 1982; Series 2 (Box R1, Folder 3)
  - Deposit records and check registers [2/3], November 1982-July 1983; Series 2 (Box R1, Folder 4)
  - Deposit records and check registers [3/3], August 1983-January 1984; Series 2 (Box R1, Folder 5)
  - General ledger FY 1983, 1982-1983; Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Financial records, 1983-1990; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - FCPAA budget, 1983-1985; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - FCPAA Treasurer's report Kevin Doss Treasurer [1/2], 1985-1986; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - FCPAA Treasurer's report Kevin Doss Treasurer [2/2], 1985-1986; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Financial statements [1/2], 1985; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Financial statements [2/2], 1985; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Income/expenses FY 1987, 1986-1987; Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Deposit records FY 1988, 1987-1988; Series 2 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Treasurer reports FY 1988, 1987-1988; Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Deposit records FY 1989, 1988-1989; Series 2 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer's report FY 1989, 1988-1989; Series 2 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Deposit records FY 1990, 1989-1990; Series 2 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - FCPAA FY 1991 accounts receivable, 1990; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - FCPAA general ledger FY 1991 [1/3], 1990; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - FCPAA general ledger FY 1991 [2/3], 1990; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - FCPAA general ledger FY 1991 [3/3], 1990; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - FCPAA accounts payable, 1990-1991; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - FCPAA tax returns, 1991-1995; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - FCPAA financial statements, 1990-1993; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - FCPAA financial statements, 1993-1998; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - FCPAA financial statements/reports, 1995 July 1- 1996 June 30; Series 2 (Box R1, Folder 6)
    Includes: Independent Auditor's Report, Balance Sheet, Summary Income Statement with Budget, Summary Income Statement Comparison with '95, Departmental Income Statements, Year to Date General Ledger/Detail Trial Balance
  - FCPAA financial records: trial balance, financial statements, year-to-date general ledger [1/2], 1996-1997; Series 2 (Box R1, Folder 7)
  - FCPAA financial records: trial balance, financial statements, year-to-date general ledger [1/2], 1996-1997; Series 2 (Box R1, Folder 8)
  - FCPAA membership account balances, 1997 June 30; Series 2 (Box R2, Folder 1)
  - FCPAA financial statements [1/4], 1997-1998; Series 2 (Box R2, Folder 2)
  - FCPAA financial statements [2/4], 1997-1998; Series 2 (Box R2, Folder 3)
  - FCPAA financial statements [3/4], 1997-1998; Series 2 (Box R2, Folder 4)
  - FCPAA financial statements [4/4], 1997-1998; Series 2 (Box R2, Folder 5)
  - Budget FY 1998, Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Has FY 1995-1998 data
  - Trial balance FY 1999 [1/3], 1998-1999; Series 2 (Box R2, Folder 6)
  - Trial balance FY 1999 [2/3], 1998-1999; Series 2 (Box R2, Folder 7)
  - Trial balance FY 1999 [3/3], 1998-1999; Series 2 (Box R2, Folder 8)
  - FCPAA monthly financial statements September-December [1/3], 2000; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - FCPAA monthly financial statements September-December [2/3], 2000; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - FCPAA monthly financial statements September-December [3/3], 2000; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - FCPAA trial balance financial statements, year to date general ledger book 1 [1/2], 2000; Series 2 (Box R3, Folder 1)
  - FCPAA trial balance financial statements, year to date general ledger book 1 [2/2], 2000; Series 2 (Box R3, Folder 2)
  - FCPAA monthly financial statements January-June [1/3], 2001; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - FCPAA monthly financial statements January-June [2/3], 2001; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - FCPAA monthly financial statements January-June [3/3], 2001; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - FCPAA financials FY 2002, 2001; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - FCPAA general ledger, 2001; Series 2 (Box R3, Folder 3)
  - FCPAA payment register, 2001; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Corporate and foundation contacts, 2001; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - CD sponsorships, 2002; Series 2 (Box R3, Folder 4)
  - Capital Club pledges FY 2003, 2002-2003; Series 2 (Box R3, Folder 5)
  - Scholarships FY 2003, 2002-2003; Series 2 (Box R3, Folder 6)
- Marketing and development records, 1984-2004; Series 3
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Active sponsor proposals, 2001; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Adam's National Bank sponsorship proposal, 1996; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Advertising sales, 1999-2000; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - American Express 16th season proposal, 1996; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - American Express 17th season proposal, 1997; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - American Express 18th season proposal, 1998; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Andy Horsley memorial, 1999; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - AT&T sponsorship proposal, 1995-1996; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Audience survey, 1995-1999; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Benefits, galas, auctions, 2002; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Bridge Builders fund, 1997-1998; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Bridge Builders fund, 1999-2000; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Capital Club, 1999; Series 3 (Box R3, Folder 7)
  - Capital Club auction, 1990; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Capital Club auction, 1991; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Capital Club auction, 1992; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Capital Club auction, 1995-1998; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Capital Club auction, 1998; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Capital Club auction, 1996; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Capital Club auction, 1997; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Capital Club auction, 1997-2001; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Capital Club auction, 1998; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Capital Club auction, 1998; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Capital Club auction, 1998; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Capital Club auction, 1998; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Capital Club auction data book part 1, 1998; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Capital Club auction data book part 2, 1998; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Capital Club auction data book part 3, 1998; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Capital Club auction, 1999; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Capital Club auction, 2000; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Capital Club auction, 2001; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Capital Club auction, 2001; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Capital Club auction, 2001-2002; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Capital Club auction, 2001; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Capital Club auction, 2002; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Capital Club auction, 2002; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Capital Club auction, 2002; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Capital Club fiscal year 2002, Series 3 (Box R3, Folder 8)
  - Capital Club mailing lists - early years, 1989-1992; Series 3 (Box R4, Folder 1)
  - Capital Club membership salute, 1989; Series 3 (Box R4, Folder 2)
  - Capital Club statement of organization and purpose, 1999; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Community donations, 2000-2001; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Community donations, prior years archives, 1996-2000; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Corporate call log, 2000-2001; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Corporate stars, 1998; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with chorus, 1990; Series 3 (Box R4, Folder 3)
  - DCTV, 1997-2000; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - DC tax exemption, 1984; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Development, 2000-2001; Series 3 (Box R4, Folder 4)
  - Development, 2001; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Donations, 1998-2000; Series 3 (Box R4, Folder 5)
  - Donations, 1998-2000; Series 3 (Box R4, Folder 6)
  - Donor committment forms, 1998; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Donor thank you letters/checks, 1998; Series 3 (Box R4, Folder 7)
  - Fact sheets, 2000; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Fall gala fundraiser, 1999; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Family & Friends, 1996; Series 3 (Box R4, Folder 8)
  - Family & Friends, 1997; Series 3 (Box R4, Folder 9)
  - Family & Friends mailers, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Family & Friends sample letters, 1999-2000; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Fiscal year 2002, Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Foundations, grants, corporate sponsorship, 1998-2001; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Foundations, grants, corporate scholarship, 1998-2001; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Fundraising, 1995-1996; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising, 1996; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising, 2001-2003; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising committee resources, 1997-2001; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising letters, 1998; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Gala, 1991; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - A Grand Night gala, 2002; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - A Grand Night gala invitations, 2002; Series 3 (Box R5, Folder 1)
  - Grant preparation materials, 1996; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Grant proposal to Bridge Builders fund, 2001; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - "Genre" magazine fundraiser, 1999; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - GMCW polo shirt, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Item 1)
  - In Memory of..., 1999; Series 3 (Box R5, Folder 2)
  - Inactive sponsor proposals, 1997-2000; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - In-kind services, 2000-2001; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - In-kind services, prior years-archives, 2000; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Invoices, 1989; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Letter to members, 1990; Series 3 (Box R5, Folder 3)
  - Mailing lists, 1999-2000; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Marketing, 1996-2000; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Marketing/PR committee, 1998-2001; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Membership directory, 1992; Series 3 (Box R5, Folder 4)
  - Microsoft giving campaign, 2002; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Capital Club correspondence, 1997-2000; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous fundraising records, 1996-1998; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - New Century prior to July 2001, Series 3 (Box R5, Folder 5)
  - New donor club, 1994-1996; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Newsletters - Capital Club, 1988-1991; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper publicity, 2004; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - NM instrumentalist appeal, 1997; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Orchestra Fund sponsors, 1999-2000; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Orchestra Fund sponsors, 1999; Series 3 (Box R5, Folder 6)
  - Parents, Families, and Friends of Lesbians and Gays Honors gala, 2002; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Pledge sheets, 1989-1990; Series 3 (Box R5, Folder 7)
  - Press clippings/reviews, 1997-2001; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Season brochure, 1999-2000; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Special gifts and acknowledgements, 1987-1999; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Under $250 FY 2002, Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - United Airlines, 1999-2000; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Web site, 2000-2001; Series 3 (Box R5, Folder 8)
- Productions, 1980-2007; Series 4
  Organized into two subseries: Administrative records and Programs.
  - Administrative records, 1980-2006; Series 4 Subseries 1
    - Newspaper publicity, 1980-1997; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Mount Saint Alban performance correspondence, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Video project, 1995-1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Box office tickets, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Eastman Kodak proposal, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - GALA V, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - GALA Festival V, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Holly Near concert, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Community performances, 1996-1997; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 9)